Welcome back.
Ladies and gentlemen.
boys and girls.
are you ready
to start the show?
Yeah!
Are you ready
to start the show?
Yeah!
Don't forget to
stay around till the very end
for a great big surprise.
Here we go!
Count with me now.
WILLIAM and CHILDREN:
Ten. nine.
eight. seven. six.
five. four. three.
two. one.
Showtime!
All right. this one?
- Come on!
- So close!
Oh. cool!
Hey.
Thank you. honey.
You seriously just gonna sit
here till the trapdoors open?
Leave her alone.
She does this every time
she's here.
Come on.
You look like someone
who could use a Freddy Fazcola.
Ew. Tastes like gasoline.
It doesn't come out for a while.
Why don't you come back to
the table and hang out with us?
They don't want me there.
No one does.
You just got
a bad roll of the dice.
Things will get better.
She's the only one
I can rely on.
who's always here for me.
That... thing down there
isn't your spirit parent
or whatever you think it is.
And it'll still be there
even if you go have
a piece of cake first.
♪ Happy birthday to you. ♪
Happy birthday!
♪ On the wire between will
and what will be ♪
♪ She's a maniac ♪
♪ Maniac on the floor... ♪
Excuse me.
- There's a boy who needs help.
- Go tell your parents.
Please. there's something wrong.
Go tell your parents!
Sir. please.
There's somebody who needs help.
- Not right now.
- Please.
Not right now.
Will anybody help me?
There's a little boy
who needs help.
- Please help me.
- I'm sorry. Adults are talking.
Run along.
Charlotte! Don't.
Hello?
MIKE
Hey. it's me.
Mike.
What time is it?
Oh. uh. it's early. Sorry.
- Did I... did I wake you up?
- No.
I mean. yes. you did. but. uh...
I had a rough night.
Bad dreams again or...?
- I can't seem to catch a break.
- Mm.
Anything that I can do to help?
No. I'm fine.
How is your day going?
Abby off to school?
Uh. not yet. She's. uh...
she's around here somewhere.
Jeremiah's on his way over
to help me
keep painting the new house.
- Great.
- Um...
I just wanted to see
if we were...
we're still good for...
for dinner later.
Yeah. Yeah.
Definitely.
It'll be good to get out.
Um. hey. I got to run.
but I'll. uh...
I'll see you later. then.
- Bye.
- Okay. Bye.
So. have you kissed her yet?
No.
Abs. it's not...
it's not like that.
We're-we're just friends.
Then why are you going
on a date?
- It's not a date.
- Then why can't I come along?
Because you can't.
That's what I thought.
Abby!
The Abbittyville Horror.
The Abbster. Word up.
What's happening?
You're growing like a weed.
Uh. I got to run.
You sure you don't want
to stay and paint?
I'll trade places with you.
Thanks. but I think
they'd notice at school.
- Probably.
- Bye.
- See you later.
- Bryson!
Bryson. wait. You dropped this.
You know. she's a good kid.
She is.
She's got a really good heart.
So. you still going on
that date with Vanessa later?
It's not a date.
Just a couple of adults
having dinner together.
you know?
Mm.
Listen. I wish you two
all the happiness in the world.
All I'm saying is
she's got crazy eyes. Mike.
She's not crazy. okay?
Ooh. speaking of crazy.
Ever since your aunt went around
telling stories
about killer teddy bears.
the whole damn town's
lost its mind.
You know. I'll be happy
when this weekend's over.
all the festival stuff's done
and people maybe just
will go back to normal.
Yeah. People are obsessed
with that old pizzeria.
Yeah. I heard they had
your aunt committed. by the way.
That's terrible.
Yeah. it's a real shame.
Hey. you sure your aunt
just made those stories up.
like. out of the blue?
Hey. you know what?
Why don't we just
keep it between you and me that
Abby's even related to her?
You know.
she's been through a lot.
and she doesn't like
that kind of attention.
So then Chica tried to shove me
into a springlock suit.
But then Mike came in.
and he had a Taser.
and he shot her
in the face with it.
I ran for the dining room
just as Foxy came off the stage
and started chasing me down.
Luckily. Vanessa saved me.
But then the Yellow Rabbit came.
and he attacked us.
He got Vanessa.
He stabbed her.
She's okay now.
So. what happened
to the Yellow Rabbit?
The springlocks went off
inside of his own suit
and crushed him alive.
They say his body's
still at Freddy's.
hidden in a secret room
that nobody's ever seen.
You're crazy.
Want to sit with us at lunch?
Sure.
Are you ever gonna go back?
To Freddy's. I mean.
I would. but...
my friends...
the animatronics are broken.
Mike says that
he'll fix them someday. but...
he's been saying that
for a while now.
Wait. so do you actually
believe anything I'm saying?
'Cause I'm pretty sure
everyone else just thinks
I'm making this stuff up.
I believe in UFOs.
And ghosts.
So why not haunted animatronics?
Young ladies.
young men. let's go.
Yeah.
Everyone. eyes to me.
I just want to. uh. remind you
that our robotics presentation
at the science fair
is this Saturday.
Some of you have been swept up
in the stupidity that is
this Freddy Fest.
Actually. Mr. Berg.
it's Fazfest.
I don't care what it's called.
It's a mockery of everything
that true robotics stands for.
We're making real robots here. people.
I want each and every one of you
to be at that science fair
on Saturday.
whether you're entering or not.
Or you can expect
a big. fat "F."
"F" for "Fazfest"?
No.
"F" for "fail."
Don't waste your time.
Let's get to work.
Miss Schmidt.
According to this.
you're planning on showing
whatever this is
Saturday at the science fair.
Certainly.
I don't have to remind you
how important this event is
to the school.
We're defending
a three-year winning streak.
I'll be ready.
Yeah. th-that's just the thing.
I don't think you will be ready.
Miss Schmidt.
robotics isn't for everyone.
There's no shame
in taking a seat
for the good of the team.
Look. look. look. what's our...
what's our school motto?
"Otters otter help each otter."
Right.
Be a good little otter.
He's rough on everyone.
Don't let him get to you.
I'm surprised you haven't tried
to fix your friends yourself.
I bet you could.
- Abs. is that you?
- Yeah.
All right. Perfect timing.
You want to do this for me?
You're hopeless.
How was your day?
Fine.
Uh. anything exciting happen?
Not really.
Okay.
There.
What would you do without me?
Thank you very much.
Okay. Uh...
Abs. I'm leaving a...
a 20 on the table
so you can...
you can order a pizza.
You remember how to call
and everything?
Of course. I'm 11.
I'm not a baby.
I know. I know.
Anything else you need from me
before I go?
You gonna watch some TV or what?
Maybe I could go see my friends.
You mean. like.
your friends from school?
I meant Chica and the others.
Those friends.
Look. Abs. we talked about this.
Okay. you can't go back there.
They're broken.
Now. one day.
I'm gonna go fix them.
but until then.
maybe you could try
making some friends
with some real kids.
My friends are real kids.
We are in
the haunted courthouse.
Did you guys hear that?
ROB
Hear what?
Look. you're right.
Abs. I'm sorry. okay?
It's just.
it's-it's complicated.
but we can talk about it later.
I have to go.
Yeah.
I love you.
Mm-hmm.
All right. don't-don't watch
too much of that show.
It'll give you nightmares. okay?
I'll be back later.
- Pardon me. sir.
- Mm. Oh.
There we are.
Thank you.
Hi.
So this is what it's like?
What?
Being normal.
Normal?
Is that... Are we...
We're normal now?
I think we're doing pretty good.
considering what
we've been through.
I just have too much time
on my hands.
It'll be better
when I can get back to work.
No. I think you're doing great.
I mean. didn't you...
you signed up for. like.
like. biking classes.
right. or...
- Spin class.
- Spin class. Yeah. yeah.
I've been going
a couple of weeks.
- Okay.
- I even made some friends.
Friends.
What's that like?
- Pardon my reach. madam.
- Oh.
They... they love
doing that here.
Um. you-you look great.
by the way.
So do you.
- This is a date.
- What?
- Did you say something?
No. I-I said... I said this is
a... a lovely day. a day.
- Day. Today's been a great day.
- Yeah.
Let me guess--
Abby tie that for you?
- She did. Yeah.
- How is she?
She's good.
Well. some days are good.
Some days. she. uh...
...she really misses them--
her "friends"--
and. uh. I don't know
how to talk to her about it.
I know you're trying
to protect her. Mike.
but this story
that they're broken.
that you're gonna fix
those animatronics.
it's only giving her false hope.
Just be honest.
Honest?
What?
Uh. nothing.
So. you want to...
tell me about your bad dream?
It's always the same.
We don't need to talk
about that.
Your dad?
Look. Vanessa. I was thinking.
do you remember how I would
use my dreams to confront
what happened with Garrett?
I mean. I admit I probably
slept a bit too much.
but it really helped me a lot.
I think it can help you. too.
I...
I-I don't think
that's a good idea.
You're never gonna be free
of your dad
until you deal with some of
the mess he left in your head.
I just... I want us to be able
to move past all of this.
You can do it.
At least try.
Just once.
Abs. I'm back.
Abby.
Abs. did you eat?
Abby? Abby?
Abby!
Hey.
Abs. I'm sorry. I...
I didn't know how to tell you.
Where are they?
I mean. there's...
pieces of them here.
pieces of them there.
No. that's not what I mean.
Where are my friends?
Look. Abs. I. um...
I don't know.
You know. maybe. um...
maybe they're in heaven.
Wouldn't you want that for them?
Yeah.
I would like that.
I'm sorry I didn't
tell you sooner. okay?
But you know what?
They're always gonna be
right here.
That's really cheesy.
- Yeah. it's a little cheesy.
- It's extremely cheesy.
All right. all right. all right.
You know what?
Come with me. I got an idea.
Okay. young lady.
You have one million tickets.
What can I get you?
Do you want some. uh... Oh.
What about orange gummy candies?
No?
Okay.
Uh. we got...
Uh. let's see. Oh.
What about this?
Oh. Oh. maybe not.
What you got there?
It's a... FazTalker.
"Realistic voice
interaction device.
Talk to us anytime."
Is that what you want?
- Yeah.
- Yeah?
Sold. One million tickets.
Let's go home.
I thought you liked
orange gummy candy.
Well. I did until I ate
that whole bag at Christmas.
Oh. And you threw it up
everywhere.
Yeah.
That was like an orange
slime waterfall.
- It was really rough.
- Don't remind me.
"
by Nine Days playing in van)
You sure I'm going
the right way?
Uh. yeah.
No. it should be up ahead.
How'd you guys find out
about this place again?
Security guard who works there.
His name is... Mike?
I don't care who he is.
as long as we have permission.
Trust me. we have
VIP treatment this time.
No breaking and entering
required.
Yeah. there. There it is.
Freddy Fazbear's Pizza.
I used to come here
when I was a kid.
Not this one you didn't.
You're thinking of
the franchise location.
This is the original.
Nobody's been here for decades.
This location came
before the other one.
So. what happened here?
Some little girl got murdered.
Whole thing got swept
under the rug.
ALEX
And now...
her soul wanders
these forgotten halls.
tortured and alone.
Dude.
Uh. sorry. You startled us.
You must be Mike.
It's Michael. actually.
Call me Michael.
So?
Are you ready for the tour?
Welcome to Freddy's.
You're cool
if we record everything?
Of course.
That's why you're here.
isn't it?
No way. They had a boat ride?
This restaurant had a lot
of unique features.
Like the Marionette.
You did your homework.
Yeah.
The Marionette truly was
one of a kind.
What's the Marionette?
The Marionette would come out
of this trapdoor on the stage
and direct
the other animatronics
- during performances.
- That's right.
Using a wireless signal.
The technology was way ahead
of its time. but...
they never made another one.
Shall we?
Whoa.
They look brand-new.
Freddy. Bonnie and Chica.
Uh. what about Foxy?
Oh. Foxy was involved in
a failed take-apart.
put-back-together attraction
and was never
quite the same again.
Kids can be so heartless.
You guys hear that?
It was. like... music or...
Uh. fair warning:
This place will prey on
your imagination if you let it.
Shall we continue?
Hey. I'm gonna catch up
to you guys.
I don't know. I wanted
to look around a little bit.
Mikey boy. let's. uh...
let's get the show on the road.
I'm burning valuable tape here.
What do we. uh...
what do we got over here?
Shit!
What the hell?
What kind of kid
would want to come here?
"Kids Cove."
Awesome.
You know. I think this might be
our best episode yet.
Yeah. usually.
we got to play it up. you know.
We have to make it
something it's not.
but this place is actually
pretty creepy.
Lisa?
Wh-What did you do?
What did you do?
Lisa? Lisa. I-I'm coming.
Where are you?
Hello?
N-N-N-N-N-No. no!
What the hell was that?
Where'd they all go?
Shit. shit. shit.
No. no. no!
Welcome back. Charlotte.
Come on.
Please work.
Please work. Please work.
Please.
I miss you guys.
Hello?
Can you guys hear me?
Chica. can you hear me?
I need you.
I miss you all so much.
All right. all right.
Welcome to the class. you guys.
Today I got a plan for you all.
so we're gonna get you guys
nice and warmed up.
Whenever you are ready.
go ahead and turn to the right.
Keep pedaling.
I'm glad you decided
to join us again.
You can do this.
Feel your core start to engage.
Another full turn to the right.
♪ When I see out of
the corner of my eye ♪
♪ "Look who's here"
and "How you doing?" ♪
♪ Why don't you tell me
who let you in... ♪
Feel your quads
start to activate.
Three. two. one.
turn to the right.
One. two. one. two.
One. two. one two.
Again. This is your moment.
Be here. Be present.
- Faster.
- You can do this.
Push it all away.
Faster.
Faster!
Please. Vanessa. easy.
You can do this.
Dad?
I'm not afraid of you.
I don't need you anymore.
I am nothing like you.
No. no. no. Come on.
Help me!
I'm not done with you.
You can't keep me here.
I'm leaving.
Don't you know
you're my favorite?
Don't you know that I love you?
Don't you know
that I care about you?
Oh.
You are my child.
You have a purpose.
Where are you gonna run to?
You will always be mine.
No!
You shall always be mine.
A...
B-B-Y.
Abby. help us.
Chica?
Chica. Chica. is that you?
Yes. Please help us.
Where are you?
Come find me.
How?
I will show you the way.
Hurry.
We are all waiting for you.
Whoa.
What is this place?
Chica?
Freddy?
Bonnie?
Chica?
Abby. you've come back to us.
Chica!
I've missed you so much.
I've missed you. too.
How did you get this new body?
Do you like it?
It's neat. but it's...
different and kind of cold.
You said you needed my help?
We do. but right now.
what matters is
we're together again.
Mike?
Abby?
Gotcha!
Haven't you ever played
hide-and-seek?
First rule is
always check behind the doors.
Right.
- Where is your brother?
- Getting breakfast.
Do you want to see
my science fair project?
It's finally done.
Wow.
You made this all by yourself?
Well. no. Chica helped.
Freddy tried.
but his fingers were too fat.
Pretty cool. right?
Very cool.
You said Freddy and Chica
helped you?
Yeah. in their old house.
last night.
It's so neat.
It's got a play area for
little kids and even a river.
Wait. A river?
Abs. I'm back.
Breakfast!
Hey. Uh. they didn't
have chocolate.
so I got banana
and. uh. blueberry.
What do we got here?
Hey. These are cool.
These are really good. Abs.
Vanessa's here.
- Hey.
We need to talk.
Yeah. we do.
What is this?
I don't understand.
Yeah. neither did I
until I called the number.
Listen. we really need
to talk about Abby.
She said she's been
with Freddy and Chica.
Yeah. it's just
this toy she has.
this new Faz-speaker thing.
No. she said she saw them.
- She said she went somewhere.
- Okay.
You know. Vanessa. I-I've...
I've been trying really hard
to-to move forward.
- I know. but. Mike...
- Um. no. listen.
How can I move forward when
it's one thing after another?
Look. I hear you. I do.
It's just what Abby said...
Abby's just a kid.
And right now she's hurting
and she misses her friends.
and there's nothing
that I can do to help her.
The same way that
I couldn't help Garrett.
Or-or the other kids
at Freddy's.
Other kids like Charlotte.
How do you...
Her dad made that flyer.
And so I called him. and he...
and he told me about
his little girl
and her best friend Vanessa.
Wh-Why didn't you tell me
that there were other victims.
other kids?
My father was a monster.
You know that.
Look. a-all I'm trying to do is
I'm trying to fix my family.
I'm trying to fix
the situation for Abby.
I'm trying to fix you.
- and-and I don't...
- Wait. W-Wait.
Is that what this
has been about?
No.
You're trying to fix me?
You know what?
I can take care of myself.
You just need
to watch out for Abby.
Hey. Abs. um...
do you think that
you can get set up without me?
You're not coming?
No. no. I'm... yeah.
I'm coming. I just. uh...
I just have to go
do something real quick.
but I-I'll be back
before it starts.
- Don't be too long. though.
- Okay.
Hey. You're gonna do great.
Thanks.
Charlotte?
It's just me. Vanessa.
Are you here
to put me back to sleep?
I know what you want.
You want to get out of here
so that you can hurt people.
The way that they hurt you.
But I can't let that happen.
I'm out of the box.
But you still
have me trapped here.
Somehow.
It's called a perimeter lock.
None of the animatronics
can leave.
Not even you.
But you can fix that.
I'm not gonna do that.
That's okay. I have another
friend who can help me now.
I don't hate you. but you need
to stay out of my way.
You're gonna be great.
honey. Don't worry.
Excuse me.
Uh. Abby.
Do you know where my booth is?
Uh. uh. I thought you decided
not to participate.
Yeah. it's a little late
to be setting up.
No. it's not. Look.
- I can set up over there.
- Look. uh.
I just don't want you
to be embarrassed. Abby.
Why would I be embarrassed?
I'm proud of my project.
Of course you are. Yeah.
So am I. Here. let me...
Let's just find the perfect
place to display it.
Oh!
Oh! Oh. oh. sorry.
I'm so. so sorry. Abby.
I-I got. uh. butterfingers. I...
I tell you what I'll do.
I'll give you full credit
for the class.
And this way. you can just
go home. and... and...
I'll take out this trash.
You're such a dick. Mr. Berg.
Who said that?
Abby. what's wrong?
Mr. Berg. he...
he destroyed
my science fair project.
I'll be your science project.
You'd do that for me?
Of course.
Well. come on. We got to hurry.
But first...
I need you to do
something for me.
Remember how I said
we needed your help?
There is a secret code
that will let me come with you.
Will you enter it for me?
Okay.
N-No!
- No!
- If you don't give me
the command to release
the perimeter lock.
I will kill her.
Charlotte. listen to me.
I know you're angry.
but it's not Abby's fault.
I know you.
I know you wouldn't hurt her.
What do I type?
Are you willing
to take that chance?
Abby!
Okay. Okay.
Okay.
Four.
A. E.
Seven.
X. C. D.
C. D.
One.
Now what?
Hit "enter."
You did it. Abby. We're free.
We better hurry
if we want to get
to the science fair in time.
I only have my bike.
How are we going to get there?
♪ 'Cause I hear it
in the night ♪
♪ I hear the secrets
that you keep ♪
♪ When you're talking
in your sleep... ♪
Where to?
Oh. you again?
You got to be kidding me.
Kid...
get out of this cab right...
Oh. my goodness!
Oh. Chica. you. uh.
dropped this.
Thank you. Abby.
I got to get a new job.
Mike?
Yeah.
Uh. thanks for seeing me.
Come on inside.
Honestly. I was surprised
to get your call.
The only calls I've gotten
so far have been...
...prank calls.
kids asking to order a pizza.
things like that.
Sure I can't offer you
a cup. Mike?
Oh. no. I'm-I'm fine. Thank you.
Um. I don't know
what I'm doing here. really.
I just. um...
I don't really have anyone else
I can talk to about this.
I'm just looking
for some answers.
You know. I...
I wasn't the best father.
I was...
I was obsessed by my work
when I was younger.
and it eventually...
cost me everything.
Including my little girl.
I'm sorry.
You know. on the phone.
you said that Charlotte died
at Freddy's?
Everyone called it an accident.
I had my suspicions about
what had really happened.
but it wasn't until years later
when those five children
went missing that...
that I knew she was murdered...
by him.
I can only assume
that you lost someone as well.
It's my little brother.
I'm sorry for your loss.
It's so easy to become
so blinded by ambition
that even with
the best of intentions
you don't see the devil
sitting right beside you.
And now this Fazfest business.
it's brought it all back.
It's an abomination.
people celebrating that place.
That's why I posted
those flyers.
- People need to know the truth.
- Wait. what...
Where-where is this?
What is this?
It's the-the river ride.
It was one of
Charlotte's favorites.
But I-I've been to Freddy's.
There's not a-a river ride.
There was only one
at the first Freddy's.
None of the later locations
had one.
First Freddy's?
Abby drew this.
Uh. c-can I use your phone?
Yeah. of course.
It's over there.
Hello?
MIKE
And you're sure she isn't there?
I'm so sorry. sir.
Apparently. there was some sort
of incident and she left.
But if you'd like.
I can call the...
What an asshole.
Is everything all right?
I. uh... I don't...
I-I don't know. Um...
I think my sister...
I think she's here.
One-two-five...
- two-five...
- Wait. wait. wait. wait.
I made this music box
for Charlotte
when she was just a baby.
The music. it helped her sleep.
I know this might sound crazy.
but if you go back there.
would you leave it for her?
Uh. yeah.
Thank you.
Abby?
Abby!
Whoa! A giant robot.
Excuse me. Pardon me.
- Look. it's Chica!
- Excuse me. Clear out.
- Whoa.
- What's going on over here?
Mr. Berg. this is my new
science fair project.
Mr. Berg.
I've heard so much about you.
Is this a joke. Miss Schmidt?
Putting someone in a suit
and passing it off
as your own work?
You're an embarrassment
to our class
and to our school. Miss Schmidt.
Now. take your freak-show friend
and get out of my science fair!
Before you lose us the title.
I'm sorry. Chica.
There is nothing
to be sorry about.
How about I go talk to him?
What are you gonna say?
I just want to see
what's going on
inside of his head.
- Whoa.
- Wow.
No.
I'm on my way.
I-I just left my keys
in my office.
Again.
This part of the building
is closed!
Now. get out of here.
Before I have you both expelled.
Geez.
I would like to talk to you
about Abby's project. Mr. Berg.
I'll give her an "A"!
You-you...
you want test answers?
I'll-I'll give you
answers to the next test.
What I want is to see
what's going on
inside of your head.
Just as I thought.
Nothing in there at all.
Abby?
Vanessa.
Are you okay?
I'm okay.
What's going on?
Where-where's Abby?
I don't know where
she is exactly. but...
she left with them.
the animatronics.
I just saw the animatronics
in-in a back room.
No. those are just prototypes
used for spare parts.
It's Charlotte.
She's behind everything.
I think Abby might be in danger.
We need to get
to the security office.
It's the only way
I know how to help her.
Come on.
I know you don't want to.
but you have to trust me.
Okay.
Is there another way?
VANESSA
Come on.
I don't understand.
Are-are the ghost kids here now?
No. there's just one ghost here.
In the Marionette.
Charlotte.
After she was killed.
I would sometimes
still see her here.
She seemed stuck
in the last emotion
before she died.
Rage.
But there's this music box
that kept her asleep.
I put her to sleep
with this music box. but...
...something or someone
broke it.
Wait. Henry just gave me
a music box.
Maybe coming this way
was a bad idea.
Hurry.
Mike.
Here. Here. Grab my hand.
Mike!
Come on.
Okay. Come on.
Come on. come on. come on.
Where are you?
Vanessa. what are we doing here?
How-how do we find Abby?
I'm trying to pull up
the tracker.
Abby thinks these animatronics
are her friends.
but they're not.
They're being wirelessly
controlled by the Marionette.
By Charlotte.
Wh-What does she want?
My father killed her.
but she doesn't blame him.
She blames the parents.
All parents.
Okay. What does she want
with my sister?
It seems like the Marionette
needs something or someone
to bond to
in order to move around.
I'm afraid it might
target Abby next.
So there's four animatronics.
and we don't know
which one has Abby.
They're all out because the
perimeter locks were disabled.
It's a system that drains
the animatronics of their power
the moment they leave
the building.
But we can find them once we
get their trackers working.
Wait.
D-Did you say
that the Marionette
controls them wirelessly?
Yeah.
Get up.
Look. you-you go...
you go into town.
find Charlotte and just try to
buy me as much time as you can.
and I'll try to disconnect
the signal from here.
Okay. Here.
We can use these.
Mike. I should have told you
about her.
I should have told you
about this place.
I-I. um...
Hey. don't worry about that
right now. okay? Just-just go.
- Please.
- Okay.
Hey. how do I close the door?
There isn't a door.
There isn't a door?
What kind of idiot
designed this place?
All right.
where the hell are you guys?
Okay.
Maybe no one will notice them.
Dude. that costume is...
Legendary.
I don't know.
Seems kind of fake to me.
- Don't be rude.
- What?
I mean. it just looks
like a toy. is all.
Hey. we're on the way
to the costume contest.
You want to come?
I do. but first.
I have to go pull the heads
off some very bad people.
Right on.
He wins.
Yeah.
Okay.
Here goes nothing.
Okay. come on.
Yes!
Vanessa.
Hey.
- Any luck over there?
- I located the first tracker.
Freddy is at 175 West Elm.
Can you get there?
Copy that. I'm close.
Harry. come inside.
You're letting in
the mosquitoes.
Mosquitoes.
mosquitoes. mosquitoes.
How is there not a door?
There's no way that'll work.
Okay.
Come on. Where are you?
Sleep tight.
CHILD
Hello?
I hate this place.
Mike. you okay?
Holy shit.
Please. come on.
Come on!
I'm going to bed.
ANNOUNCER
You're invited to Fazfest.
Come celebrate
with Bonnie. Foxy. Chica
and. of course. Freddy.
Scrumptious snacks.
marvelous merchandise...
Did you leave a door open?
I feel a draft.
You left me to die.
What? What did we do?
All of you did.
No!
Oh. God. Oh. God.
Here. Here.
You okay? It's okay.
Is there anyone else
inside of the house?
Just us. And... them.
What are they?
We need to get out of here
right now.
Come on.
Whoa!
Please. please. please.
That worked.
I'm Debbie. What's your name?
My name is Bonnie.
Can we be friends. Debbie?
Sure. we can.
Debbie.
stop talking to your animals
and go to sleep.
I'm gonna go see if your mom
will let us stay up late.
Now. if you're
headed downtown this evening.
you may want to be
on the lookout for bears.
No. the circus isn't in town.
Tonight marks
the inaugural Fazfest.
the local grassroots.
cultural arts festival
celebrating the nostalgic...
Oh. no.
Okay. Come on. Mike.
Come on.
It's now or never.
...long defunct
food and entertainment chain
began last year as a series
of urban legends
started circulating...
No.
Please don't.
Stop!
Stop. Stop.
Come on. Where is it?
Oh. Yeah.
Oh. no.
It's not working.
I have to disable the signal.
Come on.
Your mom doesn't care about you.
- Please. just stop.
- No.
She only thinks about herself.
Parents are all the same.
and I have to punish them
for that.
Please. don't hurt her.
I'm in. I'm in.
Okay.
Yes. I'm sure.
Go. go!
Go. go. go.
Do you need some help?
You all need to stay
inside tonight.
- Can they go with you?
- Of course.
You know. it looks like you
might be needing a good lawyer.
VANESSA
Mike.
I got it. Vanessa.
They're deactivated.
No. Wait.
Vanessa. th-there's one
more dot. It's still moving.
That's not possible.
- Where is it?
- It's at my house.
The Marionette.
I'm gonna head there right now.
Mike?
They're turning back on.
The signal's been reactivated.
We're outmatched.
We need more help.
I've got an idea.
I don't know
if you can hear me or not.
I-I don't even know
if you're all still here. but...
Abby needs you.
She needs your help now.
Do you hear me?
If any of you
ever really cared about her.
you're gonna help her right now.
Please!
Please. I...
I can't do this alone.
Oh. come on. come on.
Don't die.
Mike.
Mike. are you there?
My radiator's busted.
I don't know what to do.
I-I can't...
I can't get to Abby. I...
- Vanessa?
- Oh. thank God.
Do you need a ride?
I need to go to Mike's house.
Right now.
Vanessa. what is going on?
Crazy eyes.
Abby.
Vanessa.
Charlotte?
No. silly.
It's me. Abby.
Charlotte. what have you done?
Come out.
come out. wherever you are.
Vanessa.
The adults in your life
betrayed you. too.
They don't deserve
your protection.
You don't have to die with them.
You can help me.
Vanessa.
You really thought I'd forget
the first rule of hide-and-seek?
Always check behind the door.
Charlotte. listen to me.
Abby's innocent.
Just let her go.
You know. Vanessa.
I've always wondered.
what exactly goes on
inside of your head?
No. No.
Abby.
- Mike.
- Abby. Hey.
Are you okay?
I don't know what happened.
I feel sick.
It's like the bag of orange
gummy candies all over again.
- All right. c-can you stand up?
- I think so.
- Yeah? Okay.
- Let's get out of here.
- Yeah.
Come on. Come on.
No. no.
Knock. knock.
Hiya. sis.
Michael.
Vanessa. what the hell
is going on?
Oh. let me guess.
She never told you about me.
That's my sister for you.
She always was a little
selective with the truth.
I'm Michael.
Michael Afton.
I am so pleased
to finally meet you.
Leave them alone. Michael.
They haven't done
anything wrong.
I think our father might
strongly disagree with that.
Your father's dead.
Yeah.
But I'm here
to continue his legacy.
just in time for Fazfest.
That was you?
Well. your aunt was the one
who rekindled everyone's
interest in Freddy's. but...
I got to admit.
I did add fuel to the fire.
It's the perfect cover.
I mean...
we're all just
gonna blend right in.
Half of this town
will be dead by morning.
You can't do this.
This isn't a game.
Michael.
You can have a normal life.
We could have a normal life.
Vanessa. is that
what you thought?
You thought you could just
trade us in?
Betray us?
Get yourself a shiny new life?
You are his child.
You have a purpose.
We will always be his.
Come home.
I am home.
Hmm.
Doesn't matter to me anyway.
Yeah. Break their bones.
Crush them.
It's okay.
Freddy?
Abby. you've been
a very. very bad girl.
Where do you think
you're going. jackass?
Chica.
Oh. What's wrong with them?
Their systems. they're...
they're failing.
They weren't made
to leave Freddy's.
They're dying?
No. you can't die.
We're just moving on.
We can't stay
in those bodies anymore.
Are you going to heaven?
See you there someday?
But not too soon.
Mike?
Yeah?
You should know that
when we leave...
...I won't be able
to hold him anymore.
He'll get out eventually.
and he'll be stronger
than before.
Who?
Goodbye.
MIKE
Hey.
Mike?
Whoa.
Everyone okay?
Yeah. um... Hey. we got to go.
Okay.
Come on. Abby.
Stay away from us.
What?
I can't trust you.
Mike.
Just stay away.
♪ I don't know
what I was thinking ♪
♪ Leaving my child behind ♪
♪ Now I suffer the curse ♪
♪ And now I am blind ♪
♪ With all this anger.
guilt and sadness ♪
♪ Coming to haunt me forever ♪
♪ I can't wait for the cliff ♪
♪ At the end of the river ♪
♪ Is this revenge
I am seeking? ♪
♪ Or seeking someone
to avenge me? ♪
♪ Stuck in my own paradox ♪
♪ I wanna set myself free ♪
♪ Maybe I should
chase and find ♪
♪ Before they'll try
to stop it ♪
♪ It won't be long before
I'll become a puppet ♪
♪ It's been so long ♪
♪ Since I last
have seen my son ♪
♪ Lost to this monster ♪
♪ To the man
behind the slaughter ♪
♪ Since you've been gone ♪
♪ I've been singing
this stupid song ♪
♪ So I could ponder ♪
♪ The sanity of your mother. ♪
Why do we have to do this
in the rain?
Because this whole place is
getting demolished tomorrow.
We got to grab everything
we can while it's still here.
Why couldn't we just make
the props for the haunted house?
Come on. they want
the authentic thing.
The authentic
Fazbear experience.
You can't replicate that.
Just try looking around.
Anything that might trigger
a little bit of nostalgia.
Ethan. where are you?
You got something?
ETHAN
Back here!
Dude. I-I think I just found
another room.
I'm not joking-- I think
I just found another room.
Get back here right now!
- Yes. Ethan!
- Okay. okay. okay.
- You got something?
- I... Y-Yeah.
I think I found one. I-I...
I think I found a real one.
How is this still here?
It smells terrible.
Yeah. we got to take this
with us.
Let's see. uh...
- Hey. uh. Patrick. cover it.
- Yeah. yeah. yeah.
Let's get the dolly.
Cover it. will you?
Yeah. yeah. yeah. yeah.
Hey. guys. wait up!
Leaving dead space.
Three. two. one.
This message is intended
as a warning.
Mike. I wish we'd had
more time
after our conversation
about Charlotte.
but I'm sending you
this message now in case I...
I can't deliver it in person.
There are things
you need to be aware of.
I was William Afton's
business partner
for many years.
And although the equipment
I have left over
from that time is outdated.
I can still track
some of the animatronics.
Mike. the Marionette...
Mike. get out
as fast as you can.
She's coming for you.